{"type":"multiple","question":"What is Evolutionary psychology the study of?","correct_answer":"the process of human psychological evolution","incorrect_answers":["eggs", "the study of picture postcards", "sacred texts"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Which of these quotes is from the film 'Casablanca'?","correct_answer":"\"Play it, Sam. Play 'As Time goes By.'\"","incorrect_answers":["\"That’s a bingo!\"", "\"Look at me. I’m the captain now.\"", "\"Who's on first.\""]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Which of these is a soccer team based in Dallas?","correct_answer":"FC Dallas","incorrect_answers":["Dallas Bills", "Dallas United", "Real Dallas"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Which author wrote 'The Government Inspector'?","correct_answer":"Nikolai Gogol","incorrect_answers":["Virginia Woolf", "Alexander Pushkin", "Ayn Rand"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"What volcano showers ash on Sicily?","correct_answer":"Etna","incorrect_answers":["Merapi", "Fuji", "St Helen's"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"What is the capital city of Taiwan?","correct_answer":"Taipei","incorrect_answers":["Tarawa", "Beijing", "Apia"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Which actor has had roles in films including Lemony Snicket's A Series of Unfortunate Events and Kramer vs. Kramer?","correct_answer":"Dustin Hoffman","incorrect_answers":["Dan Aykroyd", "Gérard Depardieu", "Donald Sutherland"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Which film contains the character 'Charles Foster Kane'?","correct_answer":"Citizen Kane","incorrect_answers":["National Lampoon's Animal House", "It's A Wonderful Life", "Ghost"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Conakry is the capital city of which country?","correct_answer":"Guinea","incorrect_answers":["Romania", "Barbados", "Lebanon"]}{"type":"multiple","question":"Which country won the 1958 FIFA World Cup, hosted in Sweden?","correct_answer":"Brazil","incorrect_answers":["France", "Italy", "West Germany"]}"comment":"""stats":""